authpro.com 2019-04-26

# AuthPro: Privacy policy

**About Us**

This is a privacy policy for authpro.com. Our homepage on the Web is located at [ http://www.authpro.com](http://www.authpro.com/). The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at [ http://www.authpro.com/policy.shtml](http://www.authpro.com/policy.shtml)

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by e-mail at [ support@authpro.com](mailto:support@authpro.com). 

**Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals**

We have no privacy seals or other assurance mechanisms. 

**Data Collection**

P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 2 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained seperately. 

* * *

**Group "Account Holders"**

We collect the following information: 

  * User's Name
  * User's Email
  * Transaction history
  * Unique identifiers
  * IP address

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * Web site and system administration.
  * Detection if system abuse and fraudulent activity

This data will be used by authpro.com only. Authpro.com do not disclose any personal information collected on our site to any other third party.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Information requested is required to create and manage authpro.com account.

* * *

**Group "Account Members"**

We collect the following information: 

  * Unique identifiers
  * HTTP cookies
  * Transaction history
  * IP address
  * Browser information
  * Any information entered in registration form

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.

This data will be used by authpro.com and account holder for this member. Authpro.com do not disclose any personal information collected on our site to any other third party.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Information requested from account members may vary per account. Authpro.com collects login,password(optional),email(optional),ip,set cookies,other information provided in member registration form.

**Cookies**

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes: 

  * Completing the user's current activity 

**Policy Evaluation**

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 will evaluate this policy's compact policy whenever it is used with a cookie. The actions IE will take depend on what privacy level the user has selected in their browser (Low, Medium, Medium High, or High; the default is Medium. In addition, IE will examine whether the cookie's policy is considered satisfactory or unsatisfactory, whether the cookie is a session cookie or a persistent cookie, and whether the cookie is used in a first-party or third-party context. This section will attempt to evaluate this policy's compact policy against Microsoft's stated behavior for IE6. 

**Note:** this evaluation is currently experimental and should not be considered a substitute for testing with a real Web browser. 

**Satisfactory policy** : this compact policy is considered _satisfactory_ according to the rules defined by Internet Explorer 6. IE6 will accept cookies accompanied by this policy under the High, Medium High, Medium, Low, and Accept All Cookies settings.
